var data = [
  {
    category : "CRICKET",
    questions : [
      {
        points : 100,
        question : "For a cricketer, the initials “LBW” stands for …",
        answer : "Leg before wicket"
      },
      {
        points : 200,
        question :

            "The biennial international test cricket series between Australia and England is called",
        answer : "The ashes"
      },
      {
        points : 300,
        question :
            "Who was the first player to reach 10,000 runs in Test cricket?",
        answer : "Sunil Gavaskar"
      },
      {
        points : 400,
        question :
            "Which national team is nicknamed “The Proteas” or “The Springboks”?",
        answer : "South Africa"
      },
      {
        points : 500,
        question : "The highest team total record in test cricket is …",
        answer : "952"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category : "INDIA",
    questions : [
      {
        points : 100,
        question : "Number of State and Union Territories in India",
        answer : "29, 7"
      },
      {
        points : 200,
        question : "The current President of India is ______ .",
        answer : "Ram Nath Kovind"
      },
      {
        points : 300,
        question : "Which Indian city is nicknamed the 'City of Pearls'?",
        answer : "Hyderabad"
      },
      {
        points : 400,
        question : "The Palk Straits separates India and which country?",
        answer : "Sri Lanka"
      },
      {
        points : 500,
        question : "Number of Countries Where India Shares Its Border",
        answer : "8"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category : "US",
    questions : [
      {
        points : 100,
        question :
            "The Hershey Company, commonly known as Hershey, was founded in which U.S. state?",
        answer : "Pennsylvania"
      },
      {
        points : 200,
        question :
            "Which city served as the capital of the United States from 1785 until 1790?",
        answer : "New York"
      },
      {
        points : 300,
        question :
            "How many US states border the Pacific Ocean? Give names also",
        answer :
            "Five states: California, Oregon, Washington, Alaska and Hawaii"
      },
      {
        points : 400,
        question :
            "What's the only U.S. state whose name ends with three consecutive vowels?",
        answer : "Hawaii"
      },
      {
        points : 500,
        question : "What is the only U.S. state without a rectangular flag?",
        answer : "Ohio"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category : "WORLD",
    questions : [
      {
        points : 100,
        question : "What is the tallest building in the world?",
        answer : "The Burj Khalifa"
      },
      {
        points : 200,
        question :
            "The lowest natural temperature ever directly recorded at ground level was measured on what Continent?",
        answer : "Antarctica"
      },
      {
        points : 300,
        question : "Longest border in the world?",
        answer : "Australia"
      },
      {points : 400, question : "Capital of south korea?", answer : "Seoul"}, {
        points : 500,
        question : "What's the oldest continuously inhabited city the world?",
        answer : "Damascus, Syria"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category : "RIDDLE",
    questions : [
      {
        points : 100,
        question :
            "James's mom has four children. Their names are April, May, June, and ______?",
        answer : "James"
      },
      {
        points : 200,
        question : "What has 13 hearts, but no other organs?",
        answer : "A deck of cards"
      },
      {
        points : 300,
        question :
            "No matter how little or how much you use me, you change me every month. What am I?",
        answer : "A Calendar."
      },
      {
        points : 400,
        question :
            "If eleven plus two equals one, what does nine plus five equal?",
        answer :
            "11 o'clock plus 2 hours = 1 o'clock /n 9 o'clock plus 5 hours = 2 o'clock"
      },
      {
        points : 500,
        question :
            "Name the number that is three more than one-fifth of one-tenth of one-half of 5,000.",
        answer : "53"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category : "BUSINESS",
    questions : [
      {
        points : 100,
        question : "Who was the founder and chairman of Blue origin?",
        answer : "Jeffrey P. Bezos"
      },
      {
        points : 200,
        question : "Advanced Micro Devices Tag line",
        answer : "The Future Is Fusion"
      },
      {
        points : 300,
        question : "What was Lamborghini first known for?",
        answer : "Farm Tractors."
      },
      {
        points : 400,
        question : "What major corporation uses the slogan 'Go Brown'?",
        answer : "UPS"
      },
      {points : 500, question : "Who invented first car?", answer : "Karl Benz"}
    ]
  },

]